Varun Singh

Innovation, task-driven Intermediate with 1+ years self-learning experience in web design and development and other 2+ year experience in manufacturing field. Good knowledge of developing databases, creating user interfaces, writing and testing codes, troubleshooting simple/complex issues, and implementing new features.

xarun8884@gmail.com

Kashipur

github.com/varun120

8477844457

in linkedin.com/in/varun-singh-44331418a

WORK EXPERIENCE

Plant Manager

Envifreno-Products(StartUp)

06/2018 - 12/2019, Kashipur, Udham Singh Nagar

Line Engineer Bajaj Auto Pvt. Ltd.

06/2011 - 06/2012,

Pant Nagar, Udham Singh Nagar, Uttarakhand

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Virtual Assistant (08/2022 - 08/2022)

- Virtual Assistant Using Python Programming

Web Resume (07/2022 - 07/2022)

- Responsive one-page web resume using HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript.

Portfolio (05/2022 - 05/2022)

- Responsive Portfolio Using HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript.

E-commerce Website (07/2020 - 08/2020)

 Responsive E-Commerce Website using HTML/CSS/Bootstrap/MySQL/PHP.

EDUCATION

B.Tech

Birla Institute of Applied Science

07/2012 - 07/2015, Bhimtal, Nainital, Uttarakhand

- Electronics & Communication Engineering

Diploma

Government Polytechnic Shakifarm

07/2008 - 07/2011,

Sitarganj, Udham Singh Nagar, Uttarakhand

- Electronics Engineering

Intermediate

Kisan Inter Collage

06/2006 - 07/2007, Kundeshwari, Kashipur, Udham Singh Nagar, Uttarakhand

HighschoolGovernment inter collage

06/2004 - 07/2005, Patkot, Nainital, Uttarakhand

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Robotics in Spectrum-2014

• 1st Runner-Up among 8 teams, 6 colleges in Robotics in 'Spectrum - 2014', the annual fest of B.I.A.S.

(Innovate-2013) National Level Technical fest

• 1st Runner-Up among 8 teams, 12 colleges in Robotics in 'Innovate-2013', the National Level Technical fest of SRM University, Delhi NCR Campus, Ghaziabad, (U.P.).

Robotics in Spectrum-2013

• Winner among 4 teams, 4 colleges in Robotics in 'Spectrum-2013', the annual fest of B.I.A.S.

CERTIFICATES

Web Development (07/2020 - 08/2020)

Online training of WEB DEVELOPMENT the training consisted of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, SQL, and PHP modules.

Python Programming (09/2022 - 10/2022)

Online training of PYTHON PROGRAMMING from Learn Vern Pvt. Ltd.

LANGUAGES

Hindi English
Native or Bilingual Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Music Travel Coding Reading